Owen Greengo

owengreengo@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/owen-greengo-6371a1228

https://github.com/OwenMG

Summary

Aspiring web developer familiar with JavaScript, CSS, and HTML. Learning Node.js, MySQL, React, and other industry-leading technologies. Three years retail leadership experience. Led staff to top metrics in two different positions, facilitated launch of pilot program that went on to be implemented company wide.

Experience

Starbucks Barista

Quality Food Center

Mar 2022 - Present (2 months +)

Stepped down from management position in March 2022 to focus on school.

Starbucks Manager

Quality Food Center

Jan 2021 - Present (1 year 4 months +)

- •Managed a team of 3-10 as staffing fluctuated
- •Grew customer satisfaction metrics to highest in history of store location
- •Facilitated successful launch of pilot-store mobile-ordering program
- •Provided coaching and assistance to new managers in other locations

Front End Supervisor

Quality Food Center

Aug 2019 - Jan 2021 (1 year 6 months)

- •Designed and implemented employee recognition program to push metrics and job satisfaction
- •Grew and withheld front end metrics to top levels in company
- Led department of 30+ employees

Cashier

Quality Food Center

May 2019 - Aug 2019 (4 months)

Education



University of Washington Boot Camps

Full Stack Certification, Web Development

Skills

Customer Management • Training • Inventory Management • Cash Handling • Problem Solving • Supervisory Skills • Web Development • JavaScript • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • HTML